svg.com 2018-12-20

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy

Svg.com provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of Svg's website, located at the domain Svg.com (the "Svg Website"). Please note that this Privacy Policy only applies to the Svg Website.

## Information Collection and Use

It is not necessary to provide Svg with your personally identifiable information to use the Svg Website, and Svg does not collect personally identifiable information in connection with the operation of the Svg Website.  If you contact Svg by email through the Svg Website, Svg may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to Svg in your message, to respond to you.  Svg treats this information as it would treat any other unsolicited business correspondence, and has no obligation to keep this information confidential, nor to take any security measures to protect this information.

When you visit the Svg Website, Svg's servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider, the IP address will be different every time you log on. Svg uses Log Data to monitor use of the Svg Website and the services we offer via the Svg Website and for the Svg Website's technical administration.

## Cookies and Other Analytic Tools

Like many websites, Svg also uses "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Svg Website and the services offered via the Web Site. A cookie is a small data file that Svg's servers transfer to your computer's hard disk. Svg may also use tracking pixels. Tracking pixels are small graphic images, which are used in email messages to determine whether the messages were opened and the links were clicked, or are used on the Svg Website to collect information about the browser and device viewing the Svg Website. Svg does not use cookies or tracking pixels to collect personally identifiable information. 

Svg mainly uses "session cookies", which enable certain features of the Svg Website and services offered via the Svg Website, to better understand how you interact with the Web Site and services we offer via the Svg Website, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Svg Website, and to improve the Svg Website and services offered via the Svg Website. Session cookies should be deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Svg Website.

Svg also uses a persistent cookie that stays on your computer after you leave the Svg Website, for the sole purpose of ensuring that you receive a variety of Svg content (also called "frequency-capping").

## Third Party Advertisers

The Svg Website includes advertising from third party advertisers. Svg does not provide any personally identifiable information to these advertisers.

Third party advertisers, or companies working on their behalf, may serve directly to your browser the advertisements that appear on the Svg Website, which allows them to receive Log Data (as defined above). They may also use cookies, JavaScript, tracking pixels and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Svg does not control any third party advertiser tracking or measurement technologies, and the information practices of third party advertisers are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

## Opting Out

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you choose not to receive tracking pixels, you will need to disable HTML images in your email program and browser, but that may affect images in other emails you receive and the web pages you browse.

Svg also uses analytics technologies such as Google Analytics, Quantcast and comScore. For Google's privacy practices see www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html and to opt out of data recording and analysis by Google Analytics on the Svg Website, see <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. For Quantcast's privacy practices see <https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/>, and to opt out of receiving interest-based content and ads enabled by Quantcast, see https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/. For comScore's privacy practices see <http://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy> and <http://www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx>, and to opt out of having comScore associate site visits with your browser, see <http://www.scorecardresearch.com/preferences.aspx>.

Svg may allow third-party companies, including ad networks, to serve advertisements, provide other advertising services and/or collect certain information when you visit our website.

To learn more about Interest-Based Advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising by those third parties that are members of self-regulatory programs such as the Network Advertising Initiative, please visit the NAI's website <[http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)>, which will allow you to opt out of Interest-Based Advertising by one, or all, NAI members.

## Do Not Track

Some web browsers may transmit "do not track" signals to the websites and other online services with which the browser communicates. Svg currently does not take action in response to these signals. Also, please note that regardless of Svg's practices with respect to "do not track" signals, third party service providers Svg has engaged may use cookies to collect your personal information or online activities over time and across different web sites. For more information regarding Do Not Track mechanisms, see http://allaboutdnt.com/.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Svg cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties, to enforce and comply with the law. Svg may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as Svg, in its sole discretion, believes necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Svg or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

If any or all of the assets of Svg are acquired by, or merged with another entity, Svg will share with this entity some or all of the information collected through the Svg Website.

## Security

Because Svg does not collect any personally identifiable information from the Svg Website, Svg does not take any specific security measures to protect the information we do collect.

## Links to Other Sites

The Svg Website may contain links to other web sites ("Linked Sites") operated by Svg or third parties. Linked Sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. This Privacy Policy addresses only the use and disclosure of information that Svg collects through the Svg Website. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. Svg does not exercise control over third party Linked Sites. Your use of any Linked Site operated by Svg is subject to the terms and conditions provided by Svg for such Linked Site.  Svg encourages you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

## Our Policy Towards Children

The Svg Website is not directed to children under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided Svg with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact Svg at staff@Svg.com.  If Svg becomes aware that a child under 13 has provided Svg with personally identifiable information, Svg will remove such information from our files.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Svg reserves the right to change this policy at any time without prior notice. Any changes to this policy will be posted here.  You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at staff@Svg.com.

Last Update: January 6, 2017
